const PeriodicTableQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What is the vertical column on the periodic table called?",
        options: ["Group", "Period", "Block"],
        correct_option: "Group"
    },
    {
        question: "Which element is the lightest on the periodic table?",
        options: ["Hydrogen", "Oxygen", "Helium"],
        correct_option: "Hydrogen"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the horizontal row on the periodic table?",
        options: ["Period", "Group", "Block"],
        correct_option: "Period"
    },
    {
        question: "Which element is located in the same period as Oxygen?",
        options: ["Fluorine", "Nitrogen", "Carbon"],
        correct_option: "Fluorine"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the symbol for the element with atomic number 6?",
        options: ["C", "O", "N"],
        correct_option: "C"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the group number of the noble gases?",
        options: ["Group 18", "Group 1", "Group 17"],
        correct_option: "Group 18"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the symbol for the element with atomic number 1?",
        options: ["H", "He", "O"],
        correct_option: "H"
    },
    {
        question: "Which element is located in Group 17 and Period 3 of the periodic table?",
        options: ["Chlorine", "Sodium", "Potassium"],
        correct_option: "Chlorine"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the element with atomic number 26?",
        options: ["Iron", "Copper", "Gold"],
        correct_option: "Iron"
    },
    {
        question: "Which group of elements are known as the alkali metals?",
        options: ["Group 1", "Group 2", "Group 17"],
        correct_option: "Group 1"
    }
];

export default PeriodicTableQuestions;
